okay continuing our Rob timing quiz we
have seen that the multiplication now is
going to execute right commit Etc in
Cycles 358 now let's see what happens
with the ADD and multiplication here so
the question for you is when does the
add and multiply issue not that they
don't need to issue in the same cycle in
fact they won't because we can only
issue one instruction per cycle so the
question is when does the add issue and
when does the multiply issue write your
answers here for the issue
and also when do they commit write your
answer here for commit for the add and
write your answer here for the commit
for the multiply